[ED.
Happy New Year everyone! My name is Shiho Kato.
My New Year's Day is spent at home playing games and
Playing games.
I'm also thinking of building Legos.
Anyway, I am spending my time leisurely.
I went to Okinawa for a little while during New Year's.
Here's a little video from that time.
I can't hear you!
Manta-sensei!
He's smiling so much!
So cute!
Ah, manta rays!
The items I got from the Chuloami Aquarium's rummage sale.
Look!
Electrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrrr.
There are people!
So cute!
I wish you a happy new year!
Losing compos3
New Year's Day is at my parents' house and we are all having Genghis Khan today!
All the kids are all grown up now, right?
Even though they're all grown up.
Kids and lights...
I'll be 3.
Thank you, thank you, thank you. Garlic put it in there.
It's lamb, not venison.
Same dish.
Bon appétit.
Sala sala sala.
No, just one.
I'll have one too.
I'd rather have all the bean sprouts in there too.
One time, here.
Start.
You sure? I don't have to say anything.
I don't know if it's okay?
I don't know. I don't know.
But it's delicious!
I'm going to finish up with some yakiniku!
The brother in the middle really wants to be in the picture.
I think he wants to be in the picture!
Bye bye!
I took out my favorite chige miso ramen from Hidakaya.
I'm going to eat it now!
Wow, it's been a long time!
It looks so delicious!
Ta-da!
Bon appétit!
I don't talk much when it's really good.
It was really delicious!
It's the best dish I've ever had!
Thank you for the food!
I finished it!
I look forward to working with you again this year!
Hello everyone, I am back home in Yamaguchi prefecture.
I'm enjoying eating all kinds of food, including local fugu (blowfish)!
I will do my best in 2024, so please give me your best wishes for the year ahead!
I bought some deep-fried puffer fish, so I'm looking forward to eating it!
Bye bye!
Happy New Year everyone!
I'm in Kobe right now!
It's dark! Wow! Wow!
I went to Hatsumode (New Year's visit to a shrine) and my friend and I got a great lucky draw!
I also drank my first tapioca of the new year, so it's been a great start to the year!
I'll do my best this year! Bye bye!
Bye bye!
Hi, this is Kirari Takiuchi. Today I would like to eat some Hiroshima persimmons because I am back for a bit of New Year's. I like to eat them in the microwave.
I like to eat them in the microwave.
I recommend eating it with Hiroshima lemon and my favorite ponzu vinegar called Yuzu no Mura.
I hope you will try it too.
It's kind of funny that there is a dog in front of me.
Bon appétit.
Enjoy the next time! Look forward to seeing you in the next issue!
Happy New Year!
I am Hiyori Hamagishi of 46 Hyugaizuka.
I would like to go to Hatsumode with my friends now.
Yes, I will show you.
I'm going to make a "daikichi" (great fortune) with one shot.
Can you get it?
19?
Not 19.
Can you always get this?
Just a regular Shokichi?
What's that?
But it's not good luck, right?
No, it's not a "big luck".
No, it's not.
How about it?
No, I might try one more time.
Roron surprised me.
Right?
Three!
That's scary.
Okay, here we go.
Ta-da!
How's it going?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You better go.
I better go.
I think we should go.
I'll stop now
It's time to call it quits
It was today.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
Come on, come on, come on.
Onegai shimasu!
I have drawn my first fortune this year, and I would like to report the result in front of you all.
Yeah, what's this? Yeah, what's this?
Can you see it?
It says "Great Luck Later Today".
Which one?
Which is it?
Does it mean that the big lucky one will come after today?
What?
I don't know. It's my first time.
But I was with my mom.
I was with my mom.
We both came on the same day.
Number 23, today's big lucky day.
When I read it carefully, I realized that it was really good.
I read it carefully and found out that it was very good,
I am very happy.
I am so happy.
But just in case, since it is after today, I'd like to tie it up.
I am happy, happy, happy.
All right, I will do my best for the year so that this year will be another good year!
I'm waiting for your happiness.
I'm Miku Kanamura, and I'm here at Hokuryu Lake in Nagano Prefecture.
This year is the year of Tatsu, so I'm in a place that looks like it will bring me good luck.
I'm traveling with my mom, but I can't see her at all.
Last year we went to Hokkaido... and every year we see a little snow.
I'm thinking of going to my uncle's chocolate shop, so I'll take a video there too
Hi, I'm Uncle Nagano
Yes, I've been eating raw chocolate since I was little. We grew up together.
This is the main chocolate!
It's too beautiful!
This is the chocolate I always bring for the members.
It's the text of the chocolate. It's so good!
Delicious! It's made like this!
I'm going to eat a chocolate cake called Lenk.
Bon appétit!
It tastes like my uncle's chocolate.
It's delicious!
Well then...
Happy New Year, everyone. I'm Hinano Uemura. Happy New Year, everyone! My name is Hinano Uemura.
It's the year 2024.
This New Year's Day, I spent the time at home, eating ozoni (a kind of stew) and mochi (rice cakes),
I also spent my time like that, stretching my body full of frogs to keep it cool.
My goal for 2024 is to deliver my voice.
This year, I would like to work hard at voice work and singing work by accumulating training in my own way.
I also want to get to know you all better. I look forward to working with you again this year.
Happy New Year!
It's called how to spend New Year's Day.
Today, Mei-chan and I went to see a movie!
What is it?
Spy Family!
I'm looking forward to it! I'm so excited!
I bought this today!
Random, random, random.
Random, I'll open it!
I can hear LaVar's voice.
Isn't this nice?
Freedom! We're so free!
Open! Open!
I'm Yol! You're right, Yol.
I'm Anja and I'm the bondsman.
This one's cute.
I'll go for it.
Here we go.
Ready?
Se-no!
Oh, shit!
Oh, Yol!
Anya!
Beepers! Beepers!
Oh, my gosh! Cute!
That's great!
Mei loves Anja.
Whenever I see Spy Family stuff on sale
She uses Anja's to buy her own.
She also buys me Yol's stuff. He also buys me Yol's stuff.
He always does.
Thank you.
I'm so glad.
Yay!
I did it!
I'm enjoying New Year's like this!
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, yes...
I'm under the stars.
Yes?
Yes, so...
It was a New Year's video today.
But now...
My brother is taking it.
Yay!
It's just the two of us.
Today we went to my grandma's house in Nagano
and spent New Year's Day with my family!
We had a great time!
How was it? Was it good? The food?
We eat slowly at New Year's, don't we?
That's why you couldn't see your chopsticks even though you were full for life.
I ate too much, didn't I?
So, I'm going back to the Kanto area in about 3 hours.
I'm going back to the Kanto area.
Let's enjoy New Year's again next year!
I look forward to seeing you again this year!
Hello, this is Matsuda Konaka. I came to the sea of Cruz in Miyazaki Prefecture for New Year's Day.
This is where the 4th term students filmed the teaser video for their unveiling, and since I came all the way to Miyazaki, this is where I came.
I asked for everyone's continued success this year.
So I look forward to working with you again this year.
Hello everyone, my name is Rina Watanabe.
I spent New Year's reading books, playing games
I spent the New Year's day lazily reading books, playing games, and just relaxing.
This year, I would like to challenge various things
I want this year to be a fruitful year.
And since it is the year of two And since I'm two years old
I will do my best to make it to the big stage.
I will do my best.
I'm sorry for taking this picture with such shaggy hair.
I'm sorry for taking this picture.
Thank you for your support for another year.
Bye bye.
Hello everyone, this is Mana Takase.
This New Year's vacation was spent relaxing with my family. And this time I bought two new pairs of glasses.
Let me introduce them to you. Here is the first one.
Here is the first one.
The second one.
It's a pair of glasses with clay in it.
What do you think?
Like this.
It was a New Year's Day with lots of shopping!
Bye bye!
Happy New Year everyone! My name is Mizuki Hiraoka.
I went back to my hometown in Fukui and went to Hatsumode with my parents.
I drew an ema (votive picture tablet) and wrote at the shrine that I hope it will come true.
And I was very happy to find baby sponge cakes.
Here is Fukui's famous katsudon, a bowl of pork cutlet served on top of a bowl of rice in European prefecture.
It is really delicious and I hope everyone will try it.
I was relaxing with my cat like this and the ice was over in a blink of an eye.
Please look forward to seeing you again in 2024. Thank you very much.
nosso
Happy New Year to you all! I am Zionko, the little dog.
Today, I am going to show you my New Year's Day.
My relatives are here and it's very lively.
We're going to have 100 people together now, so please watch how it goes.
It's starting. We're going to do 100 people together now.
Let's open the toys for Oh-kun and Oh-kun.
The first round was Mao-chan with 22 cards, Ryoko with 17 cards, and Yuki-chan and San-En.
Good day to you, see you again.
Happy New Year!
It's the first day of the new year.
I saw the first sunrise with Tororo, so I think it's time to go back to my parents' house.
I think it's time to go back to my parents' house. I am about to go back to my parents' house
I'm going home to my parents.
Let's go home!
Every New Year's Day, my family and I play a board game called Catan.
We expand the land and the first person to get 10 points wins,
I just rolled the dice and got a 7. If I get a 7, I can move the bandit and interrupt my opponent.
White is my father, and he was doing well, so I put him in his place, thinking I would definitely get in his way.
I lost a little this year, so I will definitely win next New Year's. Happy New Year!
Happy New Year! My name is Takahashi Mikuuri.
I just finished putting on wood and came home once. I'm going to the coming-of-age ceremony now.
Yay.
Yes, I am joining the ranks of adults from today, so, well, I will do my best as myself as always.
I look forward to working with you in 2024. Good-bye.
Yes, I'll be back.
Hello! Good evening! I'm Marie Amori ex-Marie.
As some of you may know, I'm wearing a friso here.
It was Adult's Day! Wow!
Oh, here it is!
I wonder if it's called the main photo shoot today? Since we couldn't do a pre-shoot
So we took pictures today and went to the coming-of-age ceremony!
Yay!
It's nighttime now, and I went to a shrine to pay my respects while wearing this friso!
I paid my first visit to a shrine!
Yay!
It's like this!
Noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Ending
Yes! This is Hiraho. Today is the coming-of-age ceremony.
I've already done my makeup and hair since this morning, and I'm wearing frisodes, so I'm all ready to go.
Bye bye!
Today I wore frisode in Tottori prefecture.
Yay!
Let me see. Please take a turn.
Great.
Thank you.
Yellow.
Here you go, Haruyo-chan.
I'll open it. I'll open it.
It's a lovely green color.
It's green.
That's great. Thank you.
It was nice to meet you.
It's pretty full of people.
I wasn't sure if I'd see you.
I found him.
Next time.
Werewolves. Right.
We'll see you in Tokyo. Werewolf. We'll see you in Tokyo.
Okay, bye-bye.
Please subscribe to our channel!
Oh!
Oh...
But it's okay!
It's okay!
Oh, you're back!
I'm back!
Happy New Year, everyone! My name is Ishizuka and this is Maki.
I am here in Karuizawa with my family.
Wow, I am spending my days in the rich nature and bathing in negative ions.
This year will be the year I turn 20 years old, so I will do my best.
I look forward to working with you again this year.
Thank you for watching.
Happy New Year, everyone! My name is Haruka Yamashita. I am currently back in my hometown in Aichi Prefecture.
Surrounded by rape blossoms like this, here comes Yamashita's fortune-telling!
My lucky color is yellow!
Please wear yellow like me and have a lot of fun!
See you soon! Happy New Year!
Happy New Year! My name is Sunao Kosaka.
I spent New Year's Day with my family back in my hometown.
Surprisingly, I also went outside, and I think I went outside the most in 2024.
But I will do my best to get out a lot this year so that this will not be the case.
I also drew a omikuji (fortune) ticket, and it turned out to be a good one,
I believe that this year will be a good one.
It was a fun New Year's Day.
Happy New Year! My name is Hanaho Fujishima. Happy New Year! My name is Kaho Fujishima.
I'm here in the snowy mountains for my first snowboarding trip.
I'm hibernating, so I'm trying my best to be good at snow sports.
I'm hoping to be involved in Hokkaido a lot this year.
I will do my best in 2024!
Bye bye!
Are you nervous?
Yes, I'm very nervous.
Oh, you're doing it!
Kaorin
Wow!
Hello, my name is Shimizu Leah.
I would like to make oshiruko now for this New Year's Day.
Let's go for it!
How do you do this?
Oh, like this?
It's open.
Let's put it in.
Salt?
Salt. You put it in to bring out the sweetness.
I put a lot of salt.
I'd like to taste it.
It's so good!
It's ready!
Oshiroko
I'm going to eat it.
Bon appétit!
It's just like regular pee powder!
It was so easy, you guys should try making it too!
Bye bye!